frame-store.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy – FRAME

Welcome to the FRAME website located at [www.frame-store.com](https://frame-store.com/) and other related domains (“Website”). The Website is operated by Frame LA Brands, LLC (“we,” “us,” or “our”). We believe that the privacy and security of your information and data is very important. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains the type of information (“Information”) we collect from users of the Website, how that Information is used, how the Information may be shared with other parties, and what controls our users have regarding their Information. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully. Any updates or modifications to this Policy will be posted to our website on this page. By using or accessing the Website, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy. This Policy is effective as of April 1st, 2016 and was modified on May 22, 2018.  If you reside outside of the United States and use the Borderfree platform to make purchases, please consult the sections of this policy relating to the “Processing of Orders by Borderfree and the Rights of EEA Residents” and “International Data Transfers” for certain additional provisions that may apply to you.

### **Information We Collect**

If you reside in the United States or do not purchase goods through the Borderfree platform, there are two types of Information that may be collected through our Website: (1) “Personal Information” such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number, credit card number, information about your computer and other information that may be used to directly identify you, and (2) “Usage Data” which is anonymous data about your use of the Website that is not linked to you personally. 

You may enter the Website and browse its contents without submitting any Personal Information. However, if you wish to establish an account, make a purchase, participate in a contest, promotion or casting call, contact us, subscribe to our newsletter or other mailings, post any comments, or otherwise communicate with us, we may at that time require that you provide Personal Information. When you submit Personal Information on the Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to connect to our Website through a third-party social network such as Facebook (each, a “Social Network”), we may collect Personal Information from your profile on such Social Network, such as your name, username, and e-mail address, and we may publish your activity on our Website through such Social Network. In addition, our Website may offer social sharing features which will allow you to “Share” or “Like” on a Social Network. If you decide to use such features, it may allow the sharing and collection of Information both to and from such Social Network so you should check the privacy policy of each Social Network before using such features. 

We may, from time to time, give you the ability to share our Website (or features or products thereon) with your friends. In order to do so, we may ask for certain Personal Information about your friends such as their name and e-mail address. It is solely your responsibility to ensure that your friend consents to receiving what you share from us. We will only use and store your friend’s Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill your request. It will be deleted promptly after your request has been fulfilled. 

Whether or not you submit Personal Information, we may collect, store or accumulate certain Usage Data based on your use of our Website, such as information regarding which of our pages or products are most popular, the browser you use, your computer’s IP address, and the URLs you visited before and after using our Website. 

Please note that we will only collect your credit card information if you choose to purchase our products online via our Website and do not use the Borderfree platform. If you do make such an online purchase, our payment processing partner will collect your payment information and process your payment. We do not store any credit card information or share it with anyone other than our payment processor. 

### **Uses and Sharing of Information**

We use your Personal Information that we collect directly to process your requests, fulfill your orders, run our contests, promotions and casting calls, authenticate website visits/usage, inform users of relevant products and specials through promotional e-mails, maintain and develop our Website, and communicate with you. You always will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from further emails in any promotional messages we send you.

Except as described above, we will not disclose, rent, sell or share any Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes.

We do contract with companies or individuals to provide certain services including email and hosting services, software development, administration of contests, promotions and casting calls, credit card processing, shipping, data management, surveys and marketing, promotional services, etc. We call them our “Service Providers.” Such Service Providers include Borderfree, which processes certain orders for residents outside the United States. We may share both your Personal Information and Usage Data with Service Providers solely as appropriate for them to perform their functions. We do not share your credit card or other account information with third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order.

We may share your Personal Information (other than credit card information) with our affiliates and related companies. Our affiliates and related companies may contact you directly regarding certain promotions. If you would like to opt out of having us share your Personal Information with our affiliates and related companies, please e-mail us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com and include “Opt Out” in the subject line. 

Usage Data may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may share or transfer such aggregate, non-personally identifiable Usage Data with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners for administrative, analytical, research, optimization, security and other purposes, but no such information will be linked with your Personal Information or be used to identify or contact you. 

Finally, we may share your Information: (i) In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us; (ii) When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Use and other agreements; or (iii) In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. 

### **Processing of Orders by Borderfree and the Rights of EEA Residents**

If you are resident in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including countries in the European Union (“EU”) or resident in certain locations outside the United States, you may be able to purchase goods offered on our website through a facility provided by third party Borderfree Inc. (“Borderfree”).  Borderfree’s operations, including collection of personal information about users who purchase goods through its facility, are governed by its own privacy policy located at <https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/>.  If you have questions relating to Borderfree’s collection of your Personal Information, please contact Borderfree at customercare@borderfree.com.

In conjunction with your use of the Borderfree facility, you have the option to consent to provide Borderfree with certain personal data relating to you, including Personal Information, to allow Borderfree to process your orders or good through our website.  Such information may be considered “Personal Data” in the EEA under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) which is effective on May 25, 2018.  Borderfree shares certain of this Personal Data with us so that we may fulfill or process your orders, facilitate returns, and respond to customer inquiries.  If you do not provide such Personal Data, Borderfree may not be able to process your orders and we may not be able to fulfill your orders, facilitate returns or respond to customer inquiries.  During the check-out process facilitated by Borderfree you also have the option to consent to provide Personal Data to us for marketing purposes.  Your decision to provide such Personal Data through the Borderfree check out process or directly on our website is entirely optional.  We may also collect Personal Data about residents outside the United States, including residents in the EEA, when you choose to fill out forms on our website to obtain information about us or our goods.  We may combine the Personal Data that you provide through Borderfree with Personal Data provided by you directly through our website.   We use that Personal Data to provide marketing information about our goods.    

We will not share the Personal Data that we obtain through Borderfree or directly from you with third parties except as described above in regard to Personal Information.   You may withdraw your consent for us to process or retain your Personal Data by contacting us [dataprivacy@frame-brand.com](mailto:dataprivacy@frame-brand.com) with the subject line “Personal Data Request.”  If we remove your Personal Data, we may no longer be able to provide you with certain services, including processing your orders or responding to your complaints or inquiries.  You always have the right to instruct us to not process your Personal Data for marketing purposes.

If you are a resident of the EEA and wish to access or correct the Personal Data that we have about you or have any questions relating to the processing of your Personal Data, please contact us at [dataprivacy@frame-brand.com](mailto:dataprivacy@frame-brand.com) with the subject line “GDPR Data.”

### **International Data Transfers**

Personal Data that is transferred to us by Borderfree with your consent or Personal Data that you submit directly to us through our website may be stored or processed in the United States, which does not have data protection laws equivalent to those in the EEA and other jurisdictions.  If you do not wish your Personal Information to be stored or processed in the United States, please do not provide such information to Borderfree or to us.  We protect all Personal Data transferred to the United States in the same manner as we protect Personal Information.

### **Privacy and Security**

It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We take commercially reasonable and appropriate technical and organizational precautions to protect our customers' Personal Information against loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk. You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

In addition, while we take commercially reasonable steps to govern our Service Providers’ use and protection of your Personal Information, we ultimately have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such parties. As a condition to your use of the Website, you expressly agree we bear no responsibility, and are not liable in any way, for the acts, omissions or policies of our Service Providers or any other external sources with respect to your Information. 

If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third party, please immediately notify us via email at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com. 

### **Cookies**

In order to improve your user experience, we may use cookies, web beacons or similar tracking technologies. These “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, Cookies work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of the Website. Our Cookies do not generally contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this. However, not accepting Cookies may make certain features of the Website unavailable to you. Consenting to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website permits us to use cookies every time you visit our website. 

### **Children Under 13**

This website is targeted to adults. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information directly from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com. 

### **Opting Out**

When registering for an account on our Website, you will have the ability to “opt in” to receiving further promotional communications from us. Alternatively, if you initially decide to receive information from us but at a later date wish to remove your information from our database, you can do so by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. You may also at any time opt out of receiving e-mails from us or our affiliated or related companies by sending an e-mail to dataprivacy@frame-brand.com with the subject line “Opt Out.” 

Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our promotional email messages, we may still need to contact you with important transactional information related to your account and your purchases. For example, even if you have unsubscribed from our promotional emails, we will still send you confirmation of a purchase you have made on our Website. 

### **Links to Third Party Websites**

Our Website or emails may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with those websites and are not responsible for the privacy policies of any other website or their management of your Personal Information. Because they may treat your Information differently than we do, we suggest you read the privacy policies on those third party websites prior to submitting any Personal Information. 

### **Your Rights and Obligations**

We ask that you keep the Personal Information that you provide to us current and that you correct any information you have provided us by contacting us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com. You represent and warrant that all Personal Information you provide us is true and correct and relates to you and not to any other person. 

If you wish to review, delete and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with your specific request at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com; provided, however, that we reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data; and we further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such Information.  If you are a resident of the EEA and other jurisdictions outside the United States, these qualifications may not apply to you.

If you use the Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and for restricting access to your computer or device, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account. 

### **Your California Privacy Rights**

Under certain circumstances, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 states that, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, a business may be required to provide detailed information regarding how that business has shared that customer’s personal information with third parties for direct marking purposes. However, the foregoing does not apply to businesses like ours that do not disclose Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without prior approval or give customers a free mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California users may request further information about their rights under this law and our policy by writing to us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com, using the subject line “CA Request for Information,” and requesting further information. 

California Do Not Track Disclosures: Our Website does not recognize browser "Do Not Track" signals. 

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. In the event we make material changes to this Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the "Privacy" section of our Website with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Policy. If you have any questions about the changes that were implemented, please contact us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com and include “Information Regarding Updated Policy” in the subject line. In any event, your continued use of the Website after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the Website or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice. 

### **General Legal**

Our Website operates AS-IS, and we do not represent or warrant that our Website will be available at all times, or that your use of the Website will be uninterrupted or error-free. We are not responsible for your ability to access the Website or for matters beyond our control. This Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or in equity that arises out of or relates to any use of the Website will be filed only in the state or federal courts located in Los Angeles County, and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action. 

If you have questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at dataprivacy@frame-brand.com with “Website Privacy” in the subject line of your email.
